Usually we provide bean configuration details in the spring bean configuration file and we
 also specify the beans that will be injected in other beans using ref attribute. 
But Spring framework provides autowiring features too where we don’t need to provide bean injection details explicitly.

There are different ways through which we can autowire a spring bean.

autowire byName – For this type of autowiring, setter method is used for dependency injection.
 Also the variable name should be same in the class where we will inject the dependency and in 
the spring bean configuration file.
autowire byType – For this type of autowiring, class type is used. 
So there should be only one bean configured for this type in the spring bean configuration file.
autowire by constructor – This is almost similar to autowire byType, the only difference is that
 constructor is used to inject the dependency.
autowire by autodetect – If you are on Spring 3.0 or older versions, this is one of the autowire 
options available. This option was used for autowire by constructor or byType, as determined by 
Spring container. Since we already have so many options, this option is deprecated. 
I will not cover this option in this tutorial.
@Autowired annotation – We can use Spring @Autowired annotation for spring bean autowiring. 
@Autowired annotation can be applied on variables and methods for autowiring byType. 
We can also use @Autowired annotation on constructor for constructor based spring autowiring.
For @Autowired annotation to work, we also need to enable annotation based configuration in spring bean configuration file.
 This can be done by context:annotation-config element or by defining a bean of type 
org.springframework.beans.factory.annotation.AutowiredAnnotationBeanPostProcessor.

@Qualifier annotation – This annotation is used to avoid conflicts in bean mapping 
and we need to provide the bean name that will be used for autowiring. 
This way we can avoid issues where multiple beans are defined for same type. 
This annotation usually works with the @Autowired annotation. 
For constructors with multiple arguments, we can use this annotation with the argument names in the method.

[Yesterday 6:44 PM] Kadlag, Punam
What does the Spring framework do? Should I use it? Why or why not?

Spring is a framework that helps you to "wire" different components together. 
It is most useful in cases where you have a lot of components and you might 
decide to combine them in different ways, or wish to make it easy to swap out 
one component for another depending on different settings or environments.

This is what I've always understood "dependency injection" to be.

I would suggest a different definition:

"Design your objects so that they rely on an outside force to supply them with what they need, 
with the expectation that these dependencies are always injected before anybody asks them to start doing their usual jobs."

Compare that against: "Each object is responsible for going out and finding 
everything and everybody it needs as it starts up."

it looks like it necessitates a whole bunch of XML configuration

Well, most of the XML (or annotation-based) stuff is telling Spring stuff like:

When someone asks for "HammerStore", I want you to create an instance of example.HammerStore and return it.
 Cache the instance for next time, since there only needs to be one store.
When someone asks for "SomeHammer", I want you to ask yourself for a "HammerStore",
 and return the result of the store's makeHammer() method. Do not cache this result.
When someone asks for "SomeWrench", I want you to create an instance of example.WrenchImpl,
 Use the configuration setting gaugeAmount and put it into the instance's setWrenchSize() property.
 Do not cache the result.
When someone asks for "LocalPlumber", I want to you create an instance of example.PlumberImpl. 
Put the string "Pedro" into its setName() method, put a "SomeHammer" into its setHammer() method, 
and put a "SomeWrench" into its setWrench() method. Return the result, and cache the result for later since we only need one plumber.

[Yesterday 6:17 PM] Kadlag, Punam
Java code is typically written in an Integrated Development Environment (IDE) and compiled into bytecode. 
This bytecode is not readable by humans and any Java Virtual Machine (JVM) should be able to run it. 
JavaScript code is normally executed by a JavaScript engine in the same syntax in which it is written, 
although JavaScript files that are sent over the internet are often compressed into a barely readable 
format to reduce their size. Making changes in Java application environments can require several steps
 using specialized software to compile and deploy the changes, while making changes to JavaScript can
 sometimes be done with just a simple text editor.
A Beginner's Guide to Integrated Development Environments
The Web Development Series is supported by Rackspace, the better way to do hosting. 
Learn more about Rackspace's hosting solutions here. If you're new to programming (or new to programming in a par...
mashable.com
​
[Yesterday 6:18 PM] Kadlag, Punam
The biggest advantages to a JavaScript having a ability to produce the same 
result on all modern browsers.

Client-Side execution: No matter where you host JavaScript, Execute always on 
client environment to save a bandwidth and make execution process fast.

User Interface Interactivity: JavaScript used to fill web page data dynamically 
such as drop-down list for a Country and State. Base on selected Country, 
State drop down list dynamically filled. Another one is Form validation, 
missing/incorrect fields you can alert to a users using alert box.

Rapid Development: JavaScript syntax's are easy and flexible for the developers. 
JavaScript small bit of code you can test easily on Console Panel (inside Developer Tools)
 at a time browser interpret return output result. In-short easy language to get pick up in development.

Browser Compatible: The biggest advantages to a JavaScript having a 
ability to support all modern browser and produce the same result.

Make XMLHttpRequest() Object: XMLHttpRequest is special JavaScript 
object that was designed by Microsoft. XMLHttpRequest object call as
 a asynchronous HTTP request to the Server for transferring data both side without reloading the page.